KARTHIK SEELAM

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

CONTACT

+917675035615 karthikseelam077@gmail. com

SKILLS

MongoDB HTML & CSS MySQL Git Python JavaScript Java AWS Selenium

EDUCATION

CVR College of Engineering 2018-2022
B.Tech

Narayana Junior College **2016-2018**

PROFILE

I have a strong enthusiasm for the subject I study, and a year of practical experience has already given me useful experience. This passion keeps me motivated and inspires me to strive for greatness and seek out leadership roles in my sector. I've been able to swiftly pick up new talents and keep getting better because to my everlasting dedication to learning and development.

EXPERIENCE

Associate Software Engineer – Innoclique Cognitive Tech **July 2022 – Present**

Was involved in multiple projects where I obtained new skills as well as improved it throughout the time.

Developed AWS Lambda services and APIs to facilitate physician scheduling and dashboard analytics, focusing on claims processing for various healthcare providers.

Designed and implemented a physician management system, empowering physicians to track their activities and apply for leaves efficiently.

Mentored junior team members, providing guidance and support in solving complex problems and enhancing their skills

Intern - OpenText

Jan 2022 – Jul 2022

Joined the Legal Tech Team, specializing in testing frameworks such as TestNG and Junit. Additionally worked on API Automation Using Rest Assured.